Hello friends, welcome to the
technical YouTube channel. In today's video,
we will learn how to make third party insurance from ICC
in 843 at present
and what new changes have come, we will
talk about all these in great detail in this video, so
let's go live, we will show you
how to make third party
insurance of ICC from CSC, so simply
you have to go to such a portal,
as soon as you go to the CSC portal,
you have to click on the inspirational icon,
like you will click on this, you will go to
insurance, but we have to make ICC, we will
search for two
wheeler third party, you have to click on it, pay
attention here,
we have to click on two wheeler TV,
after that we will
click, it is
very simple, with this you can make a policy,
ICC Lombards is very simple,
you will see it in a very simple page, so simply
we will enter our bike's registration number here, that is, the
bike number plate, which is
RCB, we
will search here, get RTO details, so let's
enter our number plate, our bike number, after entering the number,
we will click on Get RTO details  We will check whether
it has come or not, registration date etc. model etc. Now if you want to
take personal here then you will have to click on no here,
personal accidental will not
come, after that you have to
click on that party, nothing else has to be done,
change etc. is absolutely easy,
now if we click here then
please wait processing will happen and the
premium will be shown here that how much
premium is being paid, as you can see the
premium is being paid of ₹843, now
if you want to change some details then
you can see it again by clicking on view here, it will
automatically open and the bike body will also be
shown here, if you want to add any in the vehicle description then you
can do it, otherwise let
it remain like this, after that if you
want to add a nominee from here then you can also add a nominee,
but there is no special benefit of adding a nominee in third party,
after that the
most important option here
is KYC, you will have to do KYC
because without that the further
process will not be complete, so let's
click on this now  So,
many options are available here,
you can also select Aadhaar card, PAN card or Aadhaar by going to Aadhaar,
so let's
do the verification through Aadhaar card as well,
so let's do the verification through Aadhaar card here,
we have filed some details here,
Aadhaar card, Aadhaar card number, name
etc.,
please wait and
an option will come here and your details will be
filed here automatically, here
sir some KYC will be shown, so the
thing to be noted here is that absolutely not a
single point here is automatically done
and nothing else has to be done, just
click, as soon as
you click on proceed, then
whatever details are there below here,
sir, some will be automatically verified and
click on kit propose, even your
mobile number etc. will be automatically added here
which is full in your Aadhaar card, if there is a
mismatch then
you can change the city etc. here, there is no
problem, after that click on journal propose,
enter the mail ID here  Give it after that
click on generate proposal,
like now when you click on generate proposal then it will be
please wait and you don't have to do anything,
you will click on buy no here and
your policy will be ready,
from here you can go to blue and edit and check again if there is
any problem sir, has the
detail been filled correctly here or not,
sir you will get to see something here, so
this was a new method, a
new update,
if you liked this video or you
missed something, you are facing problem in any point,
you are facing problem in understanding the story,
please comment on that too, you will get the
solution of the video, so simply click on it,
but for example, I have done the
process till here for you people, just
click on its next step.